<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NPR Correctifier Bot</title>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/corrections/</link>
    <description>Corrections from NPR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:02:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's dog Commander has left the White House</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203808674/bidens-dog-commander-has-left-the-white-house</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said the most recent biting incident was on Monday evening. In fact, it was the previous Monday, Sept. 25.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles is using AI to predict who might become homeless and help before they do</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1202374047/los-angeles-is-using-ai-to-predict-who-might-become-homeless-and-help-before-the</link>
      <description>Previous photo captions in this story misspelled Valarie Zayas' name as Valaria.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers at Kaiser Permanente are poised to go out on strike</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203547984/workers-at-kaiser-permanente-are-poised-to-go-out-on-strike</link>
      <description>A previous version of the headline misspelled Kaiser Permanente as Kaiser Permanent.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Stewart says his time on 'Star Trek' felt like a ministry</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203298903/patrick-stewart-star-trek-ministry-picard</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to replace a photo of Patrick Stewart in costume as Jean Luc Picard that had been reversed by the agency that provided it.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did we come to live extremely online? Mommy bloggers, says one writer</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/03/1203033527/how-did-we-come-to-live-extremely-online-mommy-bloggers-says-one-writer</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly used "kid" instead of "kids" in a quote from Taylor Lorenz</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 big purchases that can save energy and money at home (plus budget-friendly options)</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/03/1196977935/save-money-energy-tips</link>
      <description>A version of this story incorrectly labeled an image of an electric glass cooktop as an induction stove. The image has been removed and updated.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Carterland' puts a positive spin on an oft-disparaged presidency</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202555558/carterland-movie-jimmy-carter</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly said that President Jimmy Carter appointed Ben Bernanke to head the Federal Reserve. In fact, he appointed Paul Volcker.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's business fraud trial wraps up day one in New York</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202730320/trump-business-fraud-trial-new-york</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly included Ivanka Trump as among those who are accused of fraud. She is not.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland's dangerous eastern border takes center stage in upcoming elections</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1201688645/poland-belarus-migrants-border-wall-polish-election</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled Bialowieza, the name of a forest and town in Poland.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's in the Army now? A pitch switch aims to get more military recruits</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/01/1199543004/recruitment-military</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the first name of Lt. Col. Khrysten Grace as Kristen.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger grows over Ukraine's largest Orthodox church, aligned with Moscow despite war</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/30/1201065400/ukraine-russian-orthodox-church-tensions</link>
      <description>In a previous version of this story, we misidentified an image of a monastery in Kyiv and also inaccurately described the location of a protest rally in the Ukrainian capital.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
