<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NPR Correctifier Bot</title>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/corrections/</link>
    <description>Corrections from NPR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 06:03:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Any job can be a climate solutions job: Ask this teacher, electrician or beauty CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203426518/climate-jobs-teacher-electrician-entrepreneur</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story referred to the hair line Braidbetter as Bright Better.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI chips, shared trips, and a shorter work week</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/25/1196130707/ai-chips-shared-trips-and-a-shorter-work-week</link>
      <description>While San Juan County employees did not get a pay raise,  they did get a 4% cost of living adjustment, below the current core inflation rate.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New technology uses good old-fashioned wind to power giant cargo vessels</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/05/1200788439/wind-power-cargo-ships-carbon-emissions</link>
      <description>Previous audio and digital versions of this story said the IMO's goal was to cut the shipping industry's greenhouse gas emissions at least in half by 2050. In fact, a revised goal put out earlier this year calls for the industry to reach net zero by mid-century.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's dog Commander has left the White House</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203808674/bidens-dog-commander-has-left-the-white-house</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said the most recent biting incident was on Monday evening. In fact, it was the previous Monday, Sept. 25.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles is using AI to predict who might become homeless and help before they do</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1202374047/los-angeles-is-using-ai-to-predict-who-might-become-homeless-and-help-before-the</link>
      <description>Previous photo captions in this story misspelled Valarie Zayas' name as Valaria.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers at Kaiser Permanente are poised to go out on strike</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203547984/workers-at-kaiser-permanente-are-poised-to-go-out-on-strike</link>
      <description>A previous version of the headline misspelled Kaiser Permanente as Kaiser Permanent.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Stewart says his time on 'Star Trek' felt like a ministry</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203298903/patrick-stewart-star-trek-ministry-picard</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to replace a photo of Patrick Stewart in costume as Jean Luc Picard that had been reversed by the agency that provided it.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did we come to live extremely online? Mommy bloggers, says one writer</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/03/1203033527/how-did-we-come-to-live-extremely-online-mommy-bloggers-says-one-writer</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly used "kid" instead of "kids" in a quote from Taylor Lorenz</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 6 big purchases can save energy — and money — at home</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/03/1196977935/save-money-energy-tips</link>
      <description>A version of this story incorrectly labeled an image of an electric glass cooktop as an induction stove. The image has been removed and updated.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Carterland' puts a positive spin on an oft-disparaged presidency</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202555558/carterland-movie-jimmy-carter</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly said that President Jimmy Carter appointed Ben Bernanke to head the Federal Reserve. In fact, he appointed Paul Volcker.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's business fraud trial wraps up day one in New York</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202730320/trump-business-fraud-trial-new-york</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly included Ivanka Trump as among those who are accused of fraud. She is not.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland's dangerous eastern border takes center stage in upcoming elections</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1201688645/poland-belarus-migrants-border-wall-polish-election</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled Bialowieza, the name of a forest and town in Poland.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's in the Army now? A pitch switch aims to get more military recruits</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/01/1199543004/recruitment-military</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the first name of Lt. Col. Khrysten Grace as Kristen.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger grows over Ukraine's largest Orthodox church, aligned with Moscow despite war</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/30/1201065400/ukraine-russian-orthodox-church-tensions</link>
      <description>In a previous version of this story, we misidentified an image of a monastery in Kyiv and also inaccurately described the location of a protest rally in the Ukrainian capital.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's N.Y. business empire is 'greatly at risk' from judge's fraud ruling</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/29/1202534656/trump-fraud-ruling-new-york-business-empire-judge</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled John Coffee's surname as Coffey.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House chief of staff says it's on House Republicans to avert a shutdown</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/28/1202288527/biden-mccarthy-shutdown-zients</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that a government shutdown — rather than proposed budget cuts from House Republicans — would hurt seniors who rely on Meals on Wheels and families with kids in Head Start programs.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a government shutdown would mean for the U.S. military — and national security</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/27/1201956915/government-shutdown-us-military-national-security</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to reflect that Coast Guard members did not get paid during the 2018-2019 government shutdown.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood writers return to work, after a nearly five month strike</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/26/1201936449/writers-strike-end-vote-wga-leadership</link>
      <description>In the audio of this story, as in a previous web version, we incorrectly identify David Goodman as the current president of the WGA West. Goodman is a past president of the WGA West and current co-chair of the WGA's negotiating committee.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP rebels recall a distant era when dissidents rose up against 'Czar Cannon'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/23/1200992004/motion-to-vacate-matt-gaetz-cannon-1910</link>
      <description>A previous photo caption incorrectly said Republican Rep. Joseph Cannon of Illinois was ousted as House speaker after a revolt in 2010. In fact, he lost much of his power after a revolt in 1910 but remained speaker until the following year.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Making Us Happy: A guide to your weekend viewing and reading</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1200392962/whats-making-us-happy-a-guide-to-your-weekend-viewing-and-reading</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that in Dreaming Whilst Black, Adjani Salmon plays Kwabena, an aspiring filmmaker living with his brother and sister-in-law. In fact, Kwabena lives with his cousin and cousin's wife.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The WNBA's coming out story; plus, the dangers of sports betting</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1197953092/the-wnbas-coming-out-story-plus-the-dangers-of-sports-betting</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story suggested that New York has banned advertising of sports betting on college campuses. The New York State Gaming Commission has prohibited ads sent to people under the age of 21.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sex Education' teaches valuable lessons in empathy</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1197954209/sex-education-teaches-valuable-lessons-in-empathy</link>
      <description>A previous version of this episode incorrectly said that in Dreaming Whilst Black, Adjani Salmon plays Kwabena, an aspiring filmmaker living with his brother and sister-in-law. In fact, Kwabena lives with his cousin and cousin's wife.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Olympic gold medalist Florence 'Flo-Jo' Griffith Joyner</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/21/1200371618/remembering-olympic-gold-medalist-florence-flo-jo-griffith-joyner</link>
      <description>A previous photo caption incorrectly said Florence Griffith Joyner won a silver medal for the 200 meters at the 1988 Summer Olympic Games. In fact, she won silver for the 4x400 meter relay.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Ukraine's war drags on and a D.C. shutdown looms, Zelenskyy makes his case for aid</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/21/1200674632/zelenskyy-washington-ukraine-funding-shutdown</link>
      <description>The original version of this story correctly said that 29 Republican lawmakers signed a letter to the White House's budget director announcing they would oppose President Biden's $24 billion funding request. At one point, the story was mistakenly changed to say the letter had 28 signatories. The original figure of 29 signatories has been restored.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen. C.Q. Brown confirmed as top military officer despite Tuberville's roadblock</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/20/1200705608/senate-tuberville-hold-military-promotions</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Gen. Eric Smith was confirmed in the Senate by an 83-11 vote. The nomination was approved 96-0.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP presidential hopeful Doug Burgum says he'd leave abortion laws up to the states</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/20/1200378409/doug-burgum-president-candidate-2024</link>
      <description>In an earlier version of the transcript, a question asked by Asma Khalid was incorrectly attributed to Susan Davis.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Danish artist has been ordered to repay a museum after delivering blank canvases</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/18/1200192209/danish-artist-jens-haaning-blank-canvases-ordered-to-repay-loan-kunsten</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story listed an incorrect currency when describing a loan provided by the Kunsten Museum of Modern Art to artist Jens Haaning. The loan was provided in Danish krone.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historian Simon Schama's new book traces the roots of today's distrust of vaccines</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/16/1199963958/historian-simon-schama-new-book-traces-the-roots-of-todays-distrust-of-vaccines</link>
      <description>A previous headline misspelled Simon Schama's last name as Schema.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio's Hopewell Ceremonial Earthworks are now a UNESCO World Heritage site</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/16/1199573920/ohios-hopewell-ceremonial-earthworks-now-a-unesco-world-heritage-site</link>
      <description>A previous version of the story said Jennifer Aultman is director of historic sites and museums at Ohio History Connection. She is the organization's chief historic sites officer.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up First briefing: UAW strike; Birmingham church bombing anniversary; NPR news quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/15/1199690188/up-first-briefing-uaw-strike-birmingham-church-bombing-anniversary-npr-news-quiz</link>
      <description>This morning's newsletter incorrectly said the CDC recommends everyone 6 years and older get the new COVID-19 vaccine. In fact, it's everyone 6 months and older.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exxon minimized climate change internally after conceding that fossil fuels cause it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/14/1199570023/exxon-climate-change-fossil-fuels-global-warming-oil-gas</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly said that Exxon recently bought a company called Denbury. That acquisition has not been completed.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A corruption trial revealed a #MeToo ethics entanglement for a top Biden adviser</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1198657306/a-corruption-trial-revealed-a-metoo-ethics-entanglement-for-a-top-biden-adviser</link>
      <description>NPR updated this story to more clearly define the differences between the Time's Up Legal Defense Fund, Time's Up Now and the Time's Up Foundation.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NY Times' reporter details the struggle within the military to modernize its forces</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199222328/ny-times-reporter-details-the-struggle-within-the-military-to-modernize-its-forc</link>
      <description>The audio of this interview incorrectly refers to Haley Barbour as a former governor of Louisiana. He is a former governor of Mississippi.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mark Kelly says Biden impeachment talks are 'a distraction and a waste of time'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199168390/sen-mark-kelly-biden-impeachment-talks</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly attributed a quote about politics in the military to Sen. Mark Kelly. The statement was made by Sen. Tommy Tuberville.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich countries have to look beyond their own borders, says U.N. high commissioner</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199168397/rich-countries-have-to-look-beyond-their-own-borders-says-un-high-commissioner</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly attributed the expected number of refugees to cross into Chad by the end of this year to the U.N. Human Rights Council. In fact, it's the U.N. High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) that projects that over 600,000 refugees will arrive in Chad this year.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most California voters oppose cash reparations for slavery, poll finds</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/11/1198805444/most-california-voters-oppose-cash-reparations-for-slavery-poll-finds</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story was not clear about the work Khansa Jones-Muhammad is performing in support of reparations. She is vice-chair of the Los Angeles Reparations Advisory Commission, and is president of the National Assembly of American Slavery Descendants, a role in which she is working to launch an educational campaign on the legacy of slavery.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Star Trek' stars join the picket lines in Hollywood</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/09/1198567210/star-trek-picket-line-actors-strike</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the first name of Wil Wheaton as Will.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where *hasn't* someone escaped from prison this week? Find out in the weekly quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/08/1198068925/where-hasnt-someone-escaped-from-prison-this-week-find-out-in-the-weekly-quiz</link>
      <description>An earlier version of the homepage text for this story said it was a big week for escaped cons. Only one escapee was a convict.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting online is very risky. But hundreds of thousands of people are already doing it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/07/1192723913/internet-voting-explainer</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story said experts were unanimously against internet voting, but it is more accurate to say widespread internet voting, as some experts do think it is an acceptable practice in very limited circumstances.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biden administration proposes new federal standards for nursing home care</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/06/1197824584/the-biden-administration-proposes-new-federal-standards-for-nursing-home-care</link>
      <description>In an earlier description for this story, the name of the secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services was misspelled. He is Xavier Becerra, not Javier Becerra.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR CEO John Lansing will leave in December, capping a tumultuous year</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/05/1197104861/npr-ceo-john-lansing-leaves</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly stated the company that former NPR chief operating officer Will Lee now leads. He left NPR in June to become chief executive of Adweek.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tests negative again for COVID after the first lady tests positive</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/04/1197566021/first-lady-jill-biden-has-tested-positive-for-covid-19-again</link>
      <description>Because of incorrect information from AP, a previous photo caption misspelled Marine One as Maine One.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Richardson, former N.M. governor who worked to free Americans held abroad, dies</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/02/1197430962/bill-richardson-former-new-mexico-governor-and-diplomat-dies-at-75</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that Bill Richardson had a daughter.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new satellite will help tackle methane leaks, a major driver of global warming</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/02/1197419211/a-new-satellite-will-help-tackle-methane-leaks-a-major-driver-of-global-warming</link>
      <description>The broadcast version of this report inaccurately described the professional background of Manfredi Caltagirone. He is the head of the International Methane Emissions Observatory, but is not himself a scientist studying methane. The reference has been corrected in the story available online.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The front page of UNC's Daily Tar Heel was a gut punch. Here's the story behind it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/01/1197145404/unc-daily-tar-heel-newspaper-front-page-shooting</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story mischaracterized the sequence of mass school shootings that predated Everytown for Gun Safety's data analysis.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age ain't nothing but a number but for aging lawmakers, it's raising questions</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/01/1197120521/washington-aging-politicians-old-congress-biden-trump-mcconnell-feinstein</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story reported the wrong date of Sen. Robert Byrd's death. Byrd died on June 28, 2010.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest Gallup poll finds two-thirds of Americans approve of unions</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/30/1196712525/the-latest-gallop-poll-finds-two-thirds-of-americans-approve-of-unions</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the name of the Gallup company in the headline.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Scalise says he has been diagnosed with a 'very treatable blood cancer'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/29/1196555401/scalise-blood-cancer</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Rep. Steve Scalise was 51. He is 57.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we make college campuses safer? Expert advice after recent shootings</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/29/1196521007/unc-chapel-hill-jacksonville-shooting-campus-safety</link>
      <description>In a previous audio version of this story, we incorrectly said the shooter was asked to leave Edward Waters University in Jacksonville, Florida. In fact, when approached by a campus security officer, the shooter fled.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama requests a date to execute an inmate via nitrogen hypoxia for the first time</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196493956/alabama-death-penalty-execution-nitrogen-hypoxia</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said that Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch denied a Missouri inmate's request to be executed via nitrogen hypoxia in 2014. In fact, the denial happened in 2019.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're not welcome here!' DeSantis booed at vigil for Jacksonville shooting victims</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196305761/desantis-jacksonville-vigil-booed</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said that Florida's new permitless carry law allows people to legally own a firearm without training or a background check. In fact, the law applies to carrying a gun.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shelters are full after thousands of migrants are sent to Chicago from Texas</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196283113/shelters-are-full-after-thousands-of-migrants-are-sent-to-chicago-from-texas</link>
      <description>In this report, we incorrectly say that there are allegations of sexual misconduct against migrants housed in Chicago police stations. In fact, the charges have been filed against Chicago police officers for sexual misconduct against least one migrant housed in one police station.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A groundbreaking exhibition on the National Mall shows monuments aren't set in stone</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/27/1195465948/national-mall-monuments-playground</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the last name of Ashon T. Crawley in one sentence as Crowley.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People mourn victims of the Florida shooting as a hate crime investigation begins</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/26/1196195934/jacksonville-florida-dollar-store-shooting</link>
      <description>In an earlier version of this story, the name of one of the victims of the Jacksonville shooting was misspelled. He was identified by authorities as Jerrald De'Shaun Gallion, not Jerrald De'Shaun Gallon.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up First briefing: Trump's busy week; extremism in a hit song; 'miracle' Lahaina house</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/25/1195864509/up-first-briefing-trump-rich-men-north-of-richmond-miracle-house-lahaina</link>
      <description>Today's newsletter said Yevgeny Prigozhin was on board a plane that crashed in Russia. In fact, he was on the passenger list, so only presumed to be on the plane.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of Oliver Anthony and 'Rich Men North of Richmond'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/24/1195655023/the-rise-of-oliver-anthony-and-rich-men-north-of-richmond</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled the name of music journalist Marissa R. Moss.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trail of the Lost' is a gripping tale of hikers missing on the Pacific Crest Trail</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/24/1195262616/book-review-andrea-lankfords-trail-of-the-lost</link>
      <description>The headline on an earlier version of this book review incorrectly identified the Pacific Crest Trail as the Pacific Coast Trail. It has been corrected here.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major artists are reportedly ditching their A-list manager Scooter Braun</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/23/1195387908/why-major-artists-are-reportedly-ditching-their-a-list-manager-scooter-braun</link>
      <description>In this report, we incorrectly say Carly Rae Jepsen is one of Scooter Braun's clients. While she is listed on Braun's company website, a spokesperson for Jepsen says Braun has not managed her since 2016. Jepsen is currently with Mick Management. The story also incorrectly stated that Post Malone is one of Braun's clients.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major artists are reportedly ditching their A-list manager. Here's what's going on</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195209954/scooter-braun-ariana-grande-demi-lovato-justin-bieber</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story listed Carly Rae Jepsen as one of Scooter Braun's clients. While she is listed on Braun's company website, a spokesperson for Jepsen says Braun has not managed her since 2016. Jepsen is currently with Mick Management. The story also incorrectly stated that Post Malone is one of Braun's clients.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two families sue Florida for being kicked off Medicaid in 'unwinding' process</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/22/1195226831/two-families-sue-florida-for-being-kicked-off-medicaid-in-unwinding-process</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to protect the identity of a minor child. It was also updated to include a response from the Florida Department of Children and Families.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea level rise could drastically erode California beaches by the end of the century</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195170367/sea-level-changes-could-drastically-affect-calif-beaches-by-the-end-of-the-centu</link>
      <description>An earlier version of the story and photo caption incorrectly cited the report's prediction of California coastal erosion as 31 to 67% by the year 2100. In fact, it is 24 to 75%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
