<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NPR Corrections</title>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/corrections/</link>
    <description>Corrections from NPR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 22:09:01 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>New Mix: Bob Dylan, Sparks, Darlingside, Annie Bartholomew, more</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/06/11/1181560666/new-mix-bob-dylan-sparks-darlingside-annie-bartholomew-more</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said that Annie Bartholomew's album Sisters of White Chapel was inspired by the stories of women who came to Alaska and the Yukon Territory during the late 1900s. Those women lived during the late 19th century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/06/11/1181560666/new-mix-bob-dylan-sparks-darlingside-annie-bartholomew-more</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Carterland' puts a positive spin on an oft-disparaged presidency</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202555558/carterland-movie-jimmy-carter</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly said that President Jimmy Carter appointed Ben Bernanke to head the Federal Reserve. In fact, he appointed Paul Volcker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202555558/carterland-movie-jimmy-carter</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's business fraud trial wraps up day one in New York</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202730320/trump-business-fraud-trial-new-york</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly included Ivanka Trump as among those who are accused of fraud. She is not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202730320/trump-business-fraud-trial-new-york</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger grows over Ukraine's largest Orthodox church, aligned with Moscow despite war</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/30/1201065400/ukraine-russian-orthodox-church-tensions</link>
      <description>In a previous version of this story, we misidentified an image of a monastery in Kyiv and also inaccurately described the location of a protest rally in the Ukrainian capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/30/1201065400/ukraine-russian-orthodox-church-tensions</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House chief of staff says it's on House Republicans to avert a shutdown</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/28/1202288527/biden-mccarthy-shutdown-zients</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that a government shutdown — rather than proposed budget cuts from House Republicans — would hurt seniors who rely on Meals on Wheels and families with kids in Head Start programs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/28/1202288527/biden-mccarthy-shutdown-zients</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a government shutdown would mean for the U.S. military — and national security</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/27/1201956915/government-shutdown-us-military-national-security</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to reflect that Coast Guard members did not get paid during the 2018-2019 government shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/27/1201956915/government-shutdown-us-military-national-security</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood writers return to work, after a nearly five month strike</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/26/1201936449/writers-strike-end-vote-wga-leadership</link>
      <description>In the audio of this story, as in a previous web version, we incorrectly identify David Goodman as the current president of the WGA West. Goodman is a past president of the WGA West and current co-chair of the WGA's negotiating committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/26/1201936449/writers-strike-end-vote-wga-leadership</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP rebels recall a distant era when dissidents rose up against 'Czar Cannon'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/23/1200992004/motion-to-vacate-matt-gaetz-cannon-1910</link>
      <description>A previous photo caption incorrectly said Republican Rep. Joseph Cannon of Illinois was ousted as House speaker after a revolt in 2010. In fact, he lost much of his power after a revolt in 1910 but remained speaker until the following year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/23/1200992004/motion-to-vacate-matt-gaetz-cannon-1910</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Making Us Happy: A guide to your weekend viewing and reading</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1200392962/whats-making-us-happy-a-guide-to-your-weekend-viewing-and-reading</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that in Dreaming Whilst Black, Adjani Salmon plays Kwabena, an aspiring filmmaker living with his brother and sister-in-law. In fact, Kwabena lives with his cousin and cousin's wife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1200392962/whats-making-us-happy-a-guide-to-your-weekend-viewing-and-reading</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The WNBA's coming out story; plus, the dangers of sports betting</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1197953092/the-wnbas-coming-out-story-plus-the-dangers-of-sports-betting</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story suggested that New York has banned advertising of sports betting on college campuses. The New York State Gaming Commission has prohibited ads sent to people under the age of 21.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1197953092/the-wnbas-coming-out-story-plus-the-dangers-of-sports-betting</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sex Education' teaches valuable lessons in empathy</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1197954209/sex-education-teaches-valuable-lessons-in-empathy</link>
      <description>A previous version of this episode incorrectly said that in Dreaming Whilst Black, Adjani Salmon plays Kwabena, an aspiring filmmaker living with his brother and sister-in-law. In fact, Kwabena lives with his cousin and cousin's wife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/22/1197954209/sex-education-teaches-valuable-lessons-in-empathy</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Olympic gold medalist Florence 'Flo-Jo' Griffith Joyner</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/21/1200371618/remembering-olympic-gold-medalist-florence-flo-jo-griffith-joyner</link>
      <description>A previous photo caption incorrectly said Florence Griffith Joyner won a silver medal for the 200 meters at the 1988 Summer Olympic Games. In fact, she won silver for the 4x400 meter relay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/21/1200371618/remembering-olympic-gold-medalist-florence-flo-jo-griffith-joyner</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Ukraine's war drags on and a D.C. shutdown looms, Zelenskyy makes his case for aid</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/21/1200674632/zelenskyy-washington-ukraine-funding-shutdown</link>
      <description>The original version of this story correctly said that 29 Republican lawmakers signed a letter to the White House's budget director announcing they would oppose President Biden's $24 billion funding request. At one point, the story was mistakenly changed to say the letter had 28 signatories. The original figure of 29 signatories has been restored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/21/1200674632/zelenskyy-washington-ukraine-funding-shutdown</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen. C.Q. Brown confirmed as top military officer despite Tuberville's roadblock</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/20/1200705608/senate-tuberville-hold-military-promotions</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Gen. Eric Smith was confirmed in the Senate by an 83-11 vote. The nomination was approved 96-0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/20/1200705608/senate-tuberville-hold-military-promotions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP presidential hopeful Doug Burgum says he'd leave abortion laws up to the states</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/20/1200378409/doug-burgum-president-candidate-2024</link>
      <description>In an earlier version of the transcript, a question asked by Asma Khalid was incorrectly attributed to Susan Davis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/20/1200378409/doug-burgum-president-candidate-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Danish artist has been ordered to repay a museum after delivering blank canvases</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/18/1200192209/danish-artist-jens-haaning-blank-canvases-ordered-to-repay-loan-kunsten</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story listed an incorrect currency when describing a loan provided by the Kunsten Museum of Modern Art to artist Jens Haaning. The loan was provided in Danish krone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/18/1200192209/danish-artist-jens-haaning-blank-canvases-ordered-to-repay-loan-kunsten</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historian Simon Schama's new book traces the roots of today's distrust of vaccines</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/16/1199963958/historian-simon-schama-new-book-traces-the-roots-of-todays-distrust-of-vaccines</link>
      <description>A previous headline misspelled Simon Schama's last name as Schema.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/16/1199963958/historian-simon-schama-new-book-traces-the-roots-of-todays-distrust-of-vaccines</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio's Hopewell Ceremonial Earthworks are now a UNESCO World Heritage site</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/16/1199573920/ohios-hopewell-ceremonial-earthworks-now-a-unesco-world-heritage-site</link>
      <description>A previous version of the story said Jennifer Aultman is director of historic sites and museums at Ohio History Connection. She is the organization's chief historic sites officer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/16/1199573920/ohios-hopewell-ceremonial-earthworks-now-a-unesco-world-heritage-site</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up First briefing: UAW strike; Birmingham church bombing anniversary; NPR news quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/15/1199690188/up-first-briefing-uaw-strike-birmingham-church-bombing-anniversary-npr-news-quiz</link>
      <description>This morning's newsletter incorrectly said the CDC recommends everyone 6 years and older get the new COVID-19 vaccine. In fact, it's everyone 6 months and older.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/15/1199690188/up-first-briefing-uaw-strike-birmingham-church-bombing-anniversary-npr-news-quiz</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exxon minimized climate change internally after conceding that fossil fuels cause it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/14/1199570023/exxon-climate-change-fossil-fuels-global-warming-oil-gas</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly said that Exxon recently bought a company called Denbury. That acquisition has not been completed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/14/1199570023/exxon-climate-change-fossil-fuels-global-warming-oil-gas</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A corruption trial revealed a #MeToo ethics entanglement for a top Biden adviser</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1198657306/a-corruption-trial-revealed-a-metoo-ethics-entanglement-for-a-top-biden-adviser</link>
      <description>NPR updated this story to more clearly define the differences between the Time's Up Legal Defense Fund, Time's Up Now and the Time's Up Foundation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1198657306/a-corruption-trial-revealed-a-metoo-ethics-entanglement-for-a-top-biden-adviser</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NY Times' reporter details the struggle within the military to modernize its forces</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199222328/ny-times-reporter-details-the-struggle-within-the-military-to-modernize-its-forc</link>
      <description>The audio of this interview incorrectly refers to Haley Barbour as a former governor of Louisiana. He is a former governor of Mississippi.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199222328/ny-times-reporter-details-the-struggle-within-the-military-to-modernize-its-forc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mark Kelly says Biden impeachment talks are 'a distraction and a waste of time'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199168390/sen-mark-kelly-biden-impeachment-talks</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly attributed a quote about politics in the military to Sen. Mark Kelly. The statement was made by Sen. Tommy Tuberville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199168390/sen-mark-kelly-biden-impeachment-talks</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich countries have to look beyond their own borders, says U.N. high commissioner</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199168397/rich-countries-have-to-look-beyond-their-own-borders-says-un-high-commissioner</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly attributed the expected number of refugees to cross into Chad by the end of this year to the U.N. Human Rights Council. In fact, it's the U.N. High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) that projects that over 600,000 refugees will arrive in Chad this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/13/1199168397/rich-countries-have-to-look-beyond-their-own-borders-says-un-high-commissioner</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most California voters oppose cash reparations for slavery, poll finds</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/11/1198805444/most-california-voters-oppose-cash-reparations-for-slavery-poll-finds</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story was not clear about the work Khansa Jones-Muhammad is performing in support of reparations. She is vice-chair of the Los Angeles Reparations Advisory Commission, and is president of the National Assembly of American Slavery Descendants, a role in which she is working to launch an educational campaign on the legacy of slavery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/11/1198805444/most-california-voters-oppose-cash-reparations-for-slavery-poll-finds</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Star Trek' stars join the picket lines in Hollywood</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/09/1198567210/star-trek-picket-line-actors-strike</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the first name of Wil Wheaton as Will.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/09/1198567210/star-trek-picket-line-actors-strike</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where *hasn't* someone escaped from prison this week? Find out in the weekly quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/08/1198068925/where-hasnt-someone-escaped-from-prison-this-week-find-out-in-the-weekly-quiz</link>
      <description>An earlier version of the homepage text for this story said it was a big week for escaped cons. Only one escapee was a convict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/08/1198068925/where-hasnt-someone-escaped-from-prison-this-week-find-out-in-the-weekly-quiz</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting online is very risky. But hundreds of thousands of people are already doing it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/07/1192723913/internet-voting-explainer</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story said experts were unanimously against internet voting, but it is more accurate to say widespread internet voting, as some experts do think it is an acceptable practice in very limited circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/07/1192723913/internet-voting-explainer</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biden administration proposes new federal standards for nursing home care</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/06/1197824584/the-biden-administration-proposes-new-federal-standards-for-nursing-home-care</link>
      <description>In an earlier description for this story, the name of the secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services was misspelled. He is Xavier Becerra, not Javier Becerra.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/06/1197824584/the-biden-administration-proposes-new-federal-standards-for-nursing-home-care</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR CEO John Lansing will leave in December, capping a tumultuous year</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/05/1197104861/npr-ceo-john-lansing-leaves</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly stated the company that former NPR chief operating officer Will Lee now leads. He left NPR in June to become chief executive of Adweek.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/05/1197104861/npr-ceo-john-lansing-leaves</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tests negative again for COVID after the first lady tests positive</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/04/1197566021/first-lady-jill-biden-has-tested-positive-for-covid-19-again</link>
      <description>Because of incorrect information from AP, a previous photo caption misspelled Marine One as Maine One.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/04/1197566021/first-lady-jill-biden-has-tested-positive-for-covid-19-again</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Richardson, former N.M. governor who worked to free Americans held abroad, dies</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/02/1197430962/bill-richardson-former-new-mexico-governor-and-diplomat-dies-at-75</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that Bill Richardson had a daughter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/02/1197430962/bill-richardson-former-new-mexico-governor-and-diplomat-dies-at-75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new satellite will help tackle methane leaks, a major driver of global warming</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/02/1197419211/a-new-satellite-will-help-tackle-methane-leaks-a-major-driver-of-global-warming</link>
      <description>The broadcast version of this report inaccurately described the professional background of Manfredi Caltagirone. He is the head of the International Methane Emissions Observatory, but is not himself a scientist studying methane. The reference has been corrected in the story available online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/02/1197419211/a-new-satellite-will-help-tackle-methane-leaks-a-major-driver-of-global-warming</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The front page of UNC's Daily Tar Heel was a gut punch. Here's the story behind it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/01/1197145404/unc-daily-tar-heel-newspaper-front-page-shooting</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story mischaracterized the sequence of mass school shootings that predated Everytown for Gun Safety's data analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/01/1197145404/unc-daily-tar-heel-newspaper-front-page-shooting</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age ain't nothing but a number but for aging lawmakers, it's raising questions</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/01/1197120521/washington-aging-politicians-old-congress-biden-trump-mcconnell-feinstein</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story reported the wrong date of Sen. Robert Byrd's death. Byrd died on June 28, 2010.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/09/01/1197120521/washington-aging-politicians-old-congress-biden-trump-mcconnell-feinstein</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest Gallup poll finds two-thirds of Americans approve of unions</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/30/1196712525/the-latest-gallop-poll-finds-two-thirds-of-americans-approve-of-unions</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the name of the Gallup company in the headline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/30/1196712525/the-latest-gallop-poll-finds-two-thirds-of-americans-approve-of-unions</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Scalise says he has been diagnosed with a 'very treatable blood cancer'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/29/1196555401/scalise-blood-cancer</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Rep. Steve Scalise was 51. He is 57.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/29/1196555401/scalise-blood-cancer</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we make college campuses safer? Expert advice after recent shootings</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/29/1196521007/unc-chapel-hill-jacksonville-shooting-campus-safety</link>
      <description>In a previous audio version of this story, we incorrectly said the shooter was asked to leave Edward Waters University in Jacksonville, Florida. In fact, when approached by a campus security officer, the shooter fled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/29/1196521007/unc-chapel-hill-jacksonville-shooting-campus-safety</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama requests a date to execute an inmate via nitrogen hypoxia for the first time</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196493956/alabama-death-penalty-execution-nitrogen-hypoxia</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said that Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch denied a Missouri inmate's request to be executed via nitrogen hypoxia in 2014. In fact, the denial happened in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196493956/alabama-death-penalty-execution-nitrogen-hypoxia</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're not welcome here!' DeSantis booed at vigil for Jacksonville shooting victims</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196305761/desantis-jacksonville-vigil-booed</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said that Florida's new permitless carry law allows people to legally own a firearm without training or a background check. In fact, the law applies to carrying a gun.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196305761/desantis-jacksonville-vigil-booed</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shelters are full after thousands of migrants are sent to Chicago from Texas</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196283113/shelters-are-full-after-thousands-of-migrants-are-sent-to-chicago-from-texas</link>
      <description>In this report, we incorrectly say that there are allegations of sexual misconduct against migrants housed in Chicago police stations. In fact, the charges have been filed against Chicago police officers for sexual misconduct against least one migrant housed in one police station.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/28/1196283113/shelters-are-full-after-thousands-of-migrants-are-sent-to-chicago-from-texas</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A groundbreaking exhibition on the National Mall shows monuments aren't set in stone</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/27/1195465948/national-mall-monuments-playground</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the last name of Ashon T. Crawley in one sentence as Crowley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/27/1195465948/national-mall-monuments-playground</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People mourn victims of the Florida shooting as a hate crime investigation begins</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/26/1196195934/jacksonville-florida-dollar-store-shooting</link>
      <description>In an earlier version of this story, the name of one of the victims of the Jacksonville shooting was misspelled. He was identified by authorities as Jerrald De'Shaun Gallion, not Jerrald De'Shaun Gallon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/26/1196195934/jacksonville-florida-dollar-store-shooting</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up First briefing: Trump's busy week; extremism in a hit song; 'miracle' Lahaina house</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/25/1195864509/up-first-briefing-trump-rich-men-north-of-richmond-miracle-house-lahaina</link>
      <description>Today's newsletter said Yevgeny Prigozhin was on board a plane that crashed in Russia. In fact, he was on the passenger list, so only presumed to be on the plane.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/25/1195864509/up-first-briefing-trump-rich-men-north-of-richmond-miracle-house-lahaina</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of Oliver Anthony and 'Rich Men North of Richmond'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/24/1195655023/the-rise-of-oliver-anthony-and-rich-men-north-of-richmond</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled the name of music journalist Marissa R. Moss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/24/1195655023/the-rise-of-oliver-anthony-and-rich-men-north-of-richmond</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trail of the Lost' is a gripping tale of hikers missing on the Pacific Crest Trail</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/24/1195262616/book-review-andrea-lankfords-trail-of-the-lost</link>
      <description>The headline on an earlier version of this book review incorrectly identified the Pacific Crest Trail as the Pacific Coast Trail. It has been corrected here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/24/1195262616/book-review-andrea-lankfords-trail-of-the-lost</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major artists are reportedly ditching their A-list manager Scooter Braun</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/23/1195387908/why-major-artists-are-reportedly-ditching-their-a-list-manager-scooter-braun</link>
      <description>In this report, we incorrectly say Carly Rae Jepsen is one of Scooter Braun's clients. While she is listed on Braun's company website, a spokesperson for Jepsen says Braun has not managed her since 2016. Jepsen is currently with Mick Management. The story also incorrectly stated that Post Malone is one of Braun's clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/23/1195387908/why-major-artists-are-reportedly-ditching-their-a-list-manager-scooter-braun</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major artists are reportedly ditching their A-list manager. Here's what's going on</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195209954/scooter-braun-ariana-grande-demi-lovato-justin-bieber</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story listed Carly Rae Jepsen as one of Scooter Braun's clients. While she is listed on Braun's company website, a spokesperson for Jepsen says Braun has not managed her since 2016. Jepsen is currently with Mick Management. The story also incorrectly stated that Post Malone is one of Braun's clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195209954/scooter-braun-ariana-grande-demi-lovato-justin-bieber</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two families sue Florida for being kicked off Medicaid in 'unwinding' process</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/22/1195226831/two-families-sue-florida-for-being-kicked-off-medicaid-in-unwinding-process</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to protect the identity of a minor child. It was also updated to include a response from the Florida Department of Children and Families.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/22/1195226831/two-families-sue-florida-for-being-kicked-off-medicaid-in-unwinding-process</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea level rise could drastically erode California beaches by the end of the century</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195170367/sea-level-changes-could-drastically-affect-calif-beaches-by-the-end-of-the-centu</link>
      <description>An earlier version of the story and photo caption incorrectly cited the report's prediction of California coastal erosion as 31 to 67% by the year 2100. In fact, it is 24 to 75%.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195170367/sea-level-changes-could-drastically-affect-calif-beaches-by-the-end-of-the-centu</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burger King gave candy to a worker who never called in sick. The internet gave $400K</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1194950552/burger-king-worker-gofundme-donations</link>
      <description>An early version of this story had an incorrect number for the size of Ford's family. He has four daughters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1194950552/burger-king-worker-gofundme-donations</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan to release treated water from Fukushima nuclear plant later this week</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195165163/japan-to-release-treated-water-from-fukushima-nuclear-plant-later-this-week</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said water was used to heat nuclear fuel rods at the Fukushima plant. The water was used to cool them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/22/1195165163/japan-to-release-treated-water-from-fukushima-nuclear-plant-later-this-week</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey requires climate change education. A year in, here's how it's going</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/20/1191114786/new-jersey-requires-climate-change-education-a-year-in-heres-how-its-going</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly referred to Lauren Madden as Laura Madden. The story has been updated to include Madden's correct first name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/20/1191114786/new-jersey-requires-climate-change-education-a-year-in-heres-how-its-going</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Global heat hacks, from jazzy umbrellas in DRC to ice beans in Singapore</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2023/08/19/1194394124/photos-global-heat-hacks-from-jazzy-umbrellas-in-drc-to-ice-beans-in-singapore</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the Pance River as the Pence River.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2023/08/19/1194394124/photos-global-heat-hacks-from-jazzy-umbrellas-in-drc-to-ice-beans-in-singapore</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Filipino congregation took in its own members after their Lahaina homes burned</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/18/1194379811/a-filipino-congregation-took-in-its-own-members-after-their-lahaina-homes-burned</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the name of Estrella Arquero as Arguero.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/18/1194379811/a-filipino-congregation-took-in-its-own-members-after-their-lahaina-homes-burned</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up First briefing: Biden at Camp David; mortgage rates jump; NPR news quiz</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/18/1194569804/up-first-briefing-biden-at-camp-david-mortgage-rates-jump-npr-news-quiz</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly stated that South Korea colonized Japan. In fact, Japan colonized the Korean peninsula in the early 20th century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/18/1194569804/up-first-briefing-biden-at-camp-david-mortgage-rates-jump-npr-news-quiz</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan's companies make the world's electronics. Now they want to make weapons</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/18/1186919198/taiwan-military-weapons-manufacturing-industry</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story mistakenly said the U.S. signed a treaty requiring it to help Taiwan defend itself against China. In fact, it passed an act of legislation to help Taiwan defend itself against China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/18/1186919198/taiwan-military-weapons-manufacturing-industry</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The embattled leader of Maui County's Emergency Management Agency has resigned</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194539946/lahaina-maui-wildfires-hawaii-ema-herman-andaya-resigns</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story described "mauka" as "onto the mountainside." It's more accurate to say it is a directional indicator toward the mountain. A previous version of the clarification note above, originally posted Aug. 17, 2023, misspelled "mauka" as "makua."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194539946/lahaina-maui-wildfires-hawaii-ema-herman-andaya-resigns</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge who signed Kansas newspaper search warrant had 2 DUI arrests, reports say</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194392001/judge-who-signed-kansas-newspaper-search-warrant-had-2-dui-arrests-reports-say</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story didn't include the first name of Eric Meyer or explain that he is publisher and co-owner of the Marion County Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194392001/judge-who-signed-kansas-newspaper-search-warrant-had-2-dui-arrests-reports-say</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Give yourself grace': Camp Fire survivors offer advice to people in Maui</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194349625/maui-wildfire-advice-camp-fire-survivors</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Laura Nelson lived in her car after the fire. In fact, she stored most of her belongings in her car.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194349625/maui-wildfire-advice-camp-fire-survivors</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corruption in Afghanistan offers lessons for billions going to Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194151502/corruption-in-afghanistan-offers-lessons-for-billions-going-to-ukraine</link>
      <description>A typo misstated the amount military officials reportedly accepted for bogus documents as $10,00. The correct amount is $10,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/17/1194151502/corruption-in-afghanistan-offers-lessons-for-billions-going-to-ukraine</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leonard Bernstein's family defends appearance in 'Maestro' nose flap</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/16/1194247343/bradley-cooper-leonard-bernstein-nose</link>
      <description>This article has been updated with language that more accurately conveys concerns about Bradley Cooper's use of a prosthetic nose.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/16/1194247343/bradley-cooper-leonard-bernstein-nose</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the 6th-largest U.S. district, natural disasters have disrupted schooling for years</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/16/1193722562/puerto-rico-schools-education</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to add more detail about the changes to retirement benefits for teachers in Puerto Rico.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/16/1193722562/puerto-rico-schools-education</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking up big business is hard to do</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1193784258/breaking-up-big-business-is-hard-to-do</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said the FTC had paused its action against Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard. The FTC has paused one legal approach, but still has an appeal pending with a second legal approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1193784258/breaking-up-big-business-is-hard-to-do</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This was the hottest July ever recorded on Earth</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1192716856/july-was-the-hottest-month-ever-recorded-on-earth</link>
      <description>A previous headline incorrectly said that July was the hottest month on record. In fact, it was the hottest July on record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1192716856/july-was-the-hottest-month-ever-recorded-on-earth</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest on Ukraine: Ukraine makes some gains; China's defense minister visits Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1192649899/russia-ukraine-war-news</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly stated that tensions between Poland and Belarus have escalated in recent weeks, following the deployment of Wagner Group mercenaries to Poland. They are in Belarus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1192649899/russia-ukraine-war-news</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A lot is happening in Florida education. These are some of the changes kids will see</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1193557432/florida-education-private-schools-prageru-desantis</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said HB1 was amended to cap income eligibility for private school vouchers at 400% of the federal poverty level. The amendment eliminated income caps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/14/1193557432/florida-education-private-schools-prageru-desantis</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The riverfront brawl in Alabama reignites national debate over race</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/12/1192974338/montgomery-brawl-riverfront-race-hate-crimes</link>
      <description>An earlier photo caption incorrectly referred to a dock worker instead of a boat co-captain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/12/1192974338/montgomery-brawl-riverfront-race-hate-crimes</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The plot thickens: The battle over books comes at a cost</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/11/1192034923/the-plot-thickens-the-battle-over-books-comes-at-a-cost</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story mistakenly referred to the Denham Springs-Walker Branch library as the Dedham-Walker Springs Branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/11/1192034923/the-plot-thickens-the-battle-over-books-comes-at-a-cost</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ford is losing a lot of money in electric cars — but CEO Jim Farley is charging ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/11/1193083777/ford-electric-vehicles-f150-lightning-jim-farley</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said that Ford previously planned to sell 600,000 EVs this year. In fact, the stated goal was to hit an annual production rate of 600,000 EVs per year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/11/1193083777/ford-electric-vehicles-f150-lightning-jim-farley</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lavender Scare</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/09/1192980071/the-lavender-scare</link>
      <description>A previous version of this episode incorrectly stated that the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders is published by the American Psychological Association. It is published by the American Psychiatric Association.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/09/1192980071/the-lavender-scare</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Live Crew fought the law with its album, 'As Nasty As They Wanna Be'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/10/1193106943/hip-hops-game-changer-2-live-crews-as-nasty-as-they-wanna-be</link>
      <description>A earlier version of this story did not make clear that it was two members of the 2 Live Crew group that were arrested and one record store owner, not several employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/10/1193106943/hip-hops-game-changer-2-live-crews-as-nasty-as-they-wanna-be</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In California, wildfires are prevented by crews of unlikely firefighters: goats</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/10/1192905277/goat-grazing-california-wildfire-prevention</link>
      <description>An earlier photo caption mistakenly said a herd of 300 goats cleared out about 14,000 acres of dry brush and vegetation. In fact, it was 14 acres.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/10/1192905277/goat-grazing-california-wildfire-prevention</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Lanez sentenced to 10 years for Megan Thee Stallion shooting</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/08/1181702809/tory-lanez-megan-thee-stallion</link>
      <description>In a previous version of the web story, Megan Thee Stallion was incorrectly referred to as the plaintiff. She is the victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/08/1181702809/tory-lanez-megan-thee-stallion</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After singer David Daniels' guilty plea, the victim speaks out</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/07/1192493781/opera-singer-david-daniels-guilty-plea-victim-speaks</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story quoted Samuel Schultz as saying the guilty plea came at the ninth minute of the 11th hour. In fact he said it came at the 59th minute of the 11th hour.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/07/1192493781/opera-singer-david-daniels-guilty-plea-victim-speaks</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 people are being charged with assault for the waterfront brawl in Montgomery</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/07/1192460342/montgomery-riverfront-brawl</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly referred to the name of the city's riverboat as the Harriet II. The boat is called the Harriott II. It has also been updated to clarify that police have detained several people in connection to the brawl, and say charges are pending. Previously, the story said multiple people had been arrested.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/07/1192460342/montgomery-riverfront-brawl</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New charges against Trump focus on lies. Scholars see an authoritarian playbook</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/07/1191813216/new-charges-against-trump-focus-on-lies-scholars-see-an-authoritarian-playbook</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled Jair Bolsonaro's name as Balsonaro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/07/1191813216/new-charges-against-trump-focus-on-lies-scholars-see-an-authoritarian-playbook</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Henry Cort stole his iron innovation from Black metallurgists in Jamaica</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/03/1191989712/henry-cort-stole-his-iron-innovation-from-black-metallurgists-in-jamaica</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misstated Sheray Warmington's affiliated institution as the University of the West Indies. She is an honorary research associate at University College London (UCL). The audio version of this story misstated that the Morant Bay Rebellion was a slave rebellion. In fact, the 1865 Morant Bay Rebellion was a nuanced uprising that emerged out of growing calls for greater socioeconomic and political conditions for the Black populace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/03/1191989712/henry-cort-stole-his-iron-innovation-from-black-metallurgists-in-jamaica</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where did 20,000 Jews hide from the Holocaust? In Shanghai</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/06/1192118339/jewish-refugees-shanghai-world-war-ii</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the last name of Leiwi and Jerry Imas as Himas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/06/1192118339/jewish-refugees-shanghai-world-war-ii</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's in, who's out and storylines to watch in the Women's World Cup round of 16</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/04/1191894135/world-cup-round-of-16-knockout-stage-preview</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story said Germany beat Colombia. In fact, Germany lost to Colombia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/04/1191894135/world-cup-round-of-16-knockout-stage-preview</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly news quiz: from co-conspirators to a conspiracy about a bear suit</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/04/1191761502/weekly-news-quiz-from-co-conspirators-to-a-conspiracy-about-a-bear-suit</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this quiz said a zoo in China denied that a sun bear was not a man in a bear costume. The zoo denied that the bear was a man in a bear costume.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/04/1191761502/weekly-news-quiz-from-co-conspirators-to-a-conspiracy-about-a-bear-suit</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filling Fauci's shoes: Dr. Jeanne Marrazzo is HIV expert and a lot of fun at parties</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/04/1192015252/anthony-fauci-jeanne-marrazzo-nih-niaid-infectious-disease</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled Dr. Sharon Hillier's last name in some references.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/04/1192015252/anthony-fauci-jeanne-marrazzo-nih-niaid-infectious-disease</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Majors' trial on assault and harassment charges begins in New York</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/03/1191589920/jonathan-majors-trial-assault-harassment-new-york</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said the incident that led to Jonathan Majors' arrest occurred in March 2022. In fact, it occurred in 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/03/1191589920/jonathan-majors-trial-assault-harassment-new-york</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Medicaid dropped more than 500,000 enrollees in one month</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/03/1191416312/texas-medicaid-drops-500k-enrollees-rate-of-82-percent</link>
      <description>An earlier headline on some versions of this story was misleading. Texas Medicaid is dropping enrollees at a rate of 82% in the unwinding process, not 82% of its total enrollment. The story has been updated to clarify how many people lost Medicaid in Texas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/03/1191416312/texas-medicaid-drops-500k-enrollees-rate-of-82-percent</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston's plan to convert some school libraries into discipline centers is criticized</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/02/1191519700/houstons-plan-to-convert-some-school-libraries</link>
      <description>The headline on an earlier version of this NPR.org story mistakenly used the word "disciple" instead of "discipline."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/02/1191519700/houstons-plan-to-convert-some-school-libraries</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After a 12.3-billion-mile 'shout,' NASA regains full contact with Voyager 2</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/02/1191341035/nasa-voyager-2-spacecraft-contact</link>
      <description>A previous version of this article implied that Voyager 2 flew past Uranus in 2018 when, in fact, the spacecraft concluded its encounter with the planet and started heading toward Neptune in 1986. Voyager 2 entered interstellar space in November 2018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/02/1191341035/nasa-voyager-2-spacecraft-contact</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A jury deliberates over the sentence for the Tree of Life synagogue shooter</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/08/01/1191271560/tree-of-life-synagogue-shooter-death-penalty</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly reported that the jury gave Robert Bowers the death penalty. In fact, the jury had not announced a verdict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/08/01/1191271560/tree-of-life-synagogue-shooter-death-penalty</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Open the pod bay door, HAL' — here's how AI became a movie villain</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/31/1191017889/ai-artificial-intelligence-movies</link>
      <description>Previous audio and web versions of this story incorrectly said that Matthew Broderick's character was trying to hack the computer company's website in WarGames. In fact, it was a phone hack. Websites didn't exist in 1983.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/31/1191017889/ai-artificial-intelligence-movies</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Yellow trucking company meltdown, explained</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/30/1190960948/yellow-trucking-shutdown-explained</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to fix an incomplete sentence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/30/1190960948/yellow-trucking-shutdown-explained</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a first, the U.S. picks an Indigenous artist for a solo show at the Venice Biennale</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/29/1190952604/jeffrey-gibson-indigenous-artist-venice-biennale</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly used "cannon" instead of "canon" in a quote from Jeffrey Gibson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/29/1190952604/jeffrey-gibson-indigenous-artist-venice-biennale</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual photos at MoMA conjure the beaches, bustle and history of Lagos</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2023/07/29/1188801588/lagos-nigeria-photos-moma</link>
      <description>A previous headline incorrectly implied that Lagos is Nigeria's capital. In fact, the capital is Abuja.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2023/07/29/1188801588/lagos-nigeria-photos-moma</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has a 7th grandchild. But he's never acknowledged her, until now</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/28/1190875393/biden-grandchild-navy</link>
      <description>An earlier caption misspelled Hunter Biden's last name as Binden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/28/1190875393/biden-grandchild-navy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hulu's 'This Fool' gives a working class perspective of life in Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/28/1190820687/hulus-the-fool-gives-a-working-class-perspective-of-life-in-los-angeles</link>
      <description>"An earlier version of this story incorrectly referred to "This Fool" as "The Fool"</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/28/1190820687/hulus-the-fool-gives-a-working-class-perspective-of-life-in-los-angeles</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish singer Sinead O'Connor has died at 56</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/26/529671631/irish-singer-sinead-oconnor-has-died-at-56</link>
      <description>In the audio of this story, as in a previous web version, we incorrectly referred to Sinéad O'Connor's song as "Never Gets Old." The song is "Never Get Old."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/26/529671631/irish-singer-sinead-oconnor-has-died-at-56</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia's a big draw for China's Belt and Road plans. Finishing them is another story</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/26/1183152803/malaysia-china-belt-and-road-rail-infrastructure</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story mischaracterized Rhodium Group's assessment of whether repayments will be made on Chinese loans for its Belt and Road overseas infrastructure investments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/26/1183152803/malaysia-china-belt-and-road-rail-infrastructure</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The journey for the Emmett Till and Mamie Till-Mobley national monuments</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/25/1190066368/the-journey-for-the-emmitt-till-and-mamie-till-mobley-national-monuments</link>
      <description>An earlier headline misspelled Emmett Till's first name as Emmitt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/25/1190066368/the-journey-for-the-emmitt-till-and-mamie-till-mobley-national-monuments</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 'Someone Who Isn't Me,' Geoff Rickly recounts the struggles of some other singer</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/25/1189278437/someone-who-isnt-me-review-geoff-rickly</link>
      <description>A previous version of this review said the book's author depicted a fictional drug-abuse treatment. In fact, the medication, called ibogaine, is real and has been used in some drug-abuse treatments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/25/1189278437/someone-who-isnt-me-review-geoff-rickly</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affirmative action for rich kids: It's more than just legacy admissions</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/money/2023/07/24/1189443223/affirmative-action-for-rich-kids-its-more-than-just-legacy-admissions</link>
      <description>A previous version of this article incorrectly listed MIT as one of the universities that recently got rid of their legacy admissions program. In fact, MIT had no legacy admission program to get rid of, and there is no record of it having one in the past, according to a spokesperson for the school.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/money/2023/07/24/1189443223/affirmative-action-for-rich-kids-its-more-than-just-legacy-admissions</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter replaces its bird logo with an X as part of Elon Musk's plan for a super app</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/23/1189685146/elon-musk-twitter-logo-bird-x</link>
      <description>A previous version of the story incorrectly said Jennifer Grygiel is from the University of Syracuse. In fact, they are from Syracuse University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/23/1189685146/elon-musk-twitter-logo-bird-x</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Barbie' invites you into a Dream House stuffed with existential angst</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/07/12/1187344442/barbie-invites-you-into-a-dream-house-stuffed-with-existential-angst</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this episode implied that American Girl is competition with Mattel. American Girl is owned by Mattel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2023/07/12/1187344442/barbie-invites-you-into-a-dream-house-stuffed-with-existential-angst</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
