<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NPR Corrector Bot</title>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/corrections/</link>
    <description>Corrections from NPR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Captain found guilty of 'seaman's manslaughter' in deadly California boat fire</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/06/1211110705/california-boat-fire-2019-captain-found-guilty</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly stated what year a deadly fire took place aboard the Conception.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How two Dartmouth professors are addressing the Israeli-Palestinian conflict</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/04/1210645223/how-two-dartmouth-professors-are-addressing-student-questions-on-the-israeli-pal</link>
      <description>A previous web summary of this report misspelled Susannah Heschel's name as Heschell.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FDA expands the recall of apple cinnamon fruit pouches over lead concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/31/1209685022/wanabana-fruit-pouches-lead-fda</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story, citing the FDA, said the affected products were sold at retailers such as Sam's Club. The FDA now says Sam's Club did not sell the products.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators will travel to Antarctica after claims of sexual assault at U.S. bases</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/03/1210418182/antarctica-sexual-harassment-national-science-foundation-investigation</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story mistakenly said that investigators will be spending the next two weeks examining reports of sexual misconduct at U.S. research bases on Antarctica. Investigators will be arriving to prepare for a future on-site presence in Antarctica.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm X arrives — finally — at New York's Metropolitan Opera</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/03/1210208373/malcolm-x-opera</link>
      <description>A previous version of this feature stated that the Metropolitan Opera has only presented one other opera by a Black composer previous to X. In fact, the Met has presented two operas by Terence Blanchard since 2021: Fire Shut Up in My Bones and Champion. Anthony Davis is still the second Black composer to have his work presented by the Met.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six things to know about the political debate around daylight saving time</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/02/1210212060/daylight-saving-time-states-2023</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story said Samoa doesn't observe daylight saving time. In fact, American Samoa doesn't observe it.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everybody got it wrong': How did Israel fail to detect Hamas' planned invasion?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/02/1210076717/everybody-got-it-wrong-how-did-israel-fail-to-detect-hamas-planned-invasion</link>
      <description>In this interview, Terry Gross misidentified Mohammed bin Salman as the ruler of Iran. In fact, he is the crown prince of Saudi Arabia.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ady Barkan, activist who championed health care reform, dies of ALS at 39</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/02/1210117475/ady-barkan-als-activist-obituary</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Barkan's death was announced on Monday. His death happened and was announced on Wednesday.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Americans and other foreign nationals leave besieged Gaza</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/01/1209859350/foreign-nationals-gaza-rafah-border</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled Wafa Elsaka's name.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To control rabies in wildlife, the USDA drops vaccine treats from the sky</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/01/1198908463/raccoon-rabies-usda-vaccination-program-airdrop-oral-vaccine</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled Emily Mullin's last name as Mullen.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Department punishes student loan servicer for billing mistakes</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/31/1209464901/education-department-punishes-student-loan-servicer-billing-mistakes-mohela</link>
      <description>A previous version of this digital story incorrectly identified MOHELA as the largest federal student loan servicer. In fact, it is one of the largest loan servicers.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza residents break into U.N. warehouse for supplies as Israeli barrage continues</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/29/1209307843/gaza-residents-break-into-u-n-warehouse-for-supplies-as-israeli-barrage-continue</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misidentified Benjamin Netanyahu as the president of Israel. Netanyahu is Israel's prime minister.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Unmarked Graveyard' digs into the mysteries surrounding author Dawn Powell</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/28/1209273923/the-unmarked-graveyard-digs-into-the-mysteries-surrounding-author-dawn-powell</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly stated that today, Dawn Powell's son would be diagnosed as having cerebral palsy and schizophrenia. Per Powell's biographer, Tim Page, today Dawn Powell's son would actually be diagnosed with autism.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Three Faces of Ataturk</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/26/1198908163/the-three-faces-of-ataturk</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this episode incorrectly said that the word "genocide" was first used to describe actions taken by Ottomans against Armenians. Most historians view the series of massacres and displacements of Armenians started by Ottoman forces in 1915 as a "genocide,"but the word "genocide" was not coined until 1944. Turkey denies the label, "genocide," and says the deaths came amid widespread regional conflict.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Majors' trial for assault and harassment charges rescheduled again</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/25/1191589920/jonathan-majors-trial-assault-harassment-new-york</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said the incident that led to Jonathan Majors' arrest occurred in March 2022. In fact, it occurred in 2023.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny deer and rising seas: How climate change is testing the Endangered Species Act</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/25/1198908368/florida-key-deer-endangered</link>
      <description>In the audio of this episode, we incorrectly stated that Valerie Preziosi is the founder of Key Deer Alliance. In fact, she is the founder of the organization Save Our Key Deer.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freed Israeli hostage: Hamas kidnapping was 'hell'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/24/1208170863/israeli-hamas-gaza-hostages</link>
      <description>NPR has updated this story to reflect a more accurate translation of Yocheved Lifshitz's statement describing her time in captivity as "hell," rather than a "nightmare" as previously published.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How IBM's gamble ushered in the computer age</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/23/1197956188/the-indicator-watson-jr-ibm-big-gamble</link>
      <description>In a previous version of this episode, we stated that Thomas Watson Jr. fought on the side of the United States in World War II while IBM, under his father's leadership, was doing business with the Nazi regime. As a World War II pilot, Watson didn't fight in combat missions, but some of his missions did take him through combat zones where he faced enemy fire. And while IBM did sell technology to the Nazi government in the years leading up to the U.S.'s involvement in World War II, by the time the U.S. entered the war and Watson was serving in the war, the German government had seized the assets of American companies, curtailing IBM's control over its German operations.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An off-duty pilot attempted to shut off the engines in flight, Alaska Airlines says</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/23/1208009872/off-duty-pilot-attempted-to-shut-off-the-engines-in-flight-alaska-airlines</link>
      <description>In an earlier version of this story, we incorrectly reported that flight attendants were permitted to occupy a jump seat in the flight deck.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians brace for more violence after reprisal attacks in the West Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/20/1207543936/israel-palestine-hamas-west-bank</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story said a lawyer had told NPR of shootings of Palestinians.  In fact the lawyer told of shootings of Israelis.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using AI, cartoonist Amy Kurzweil connects with deceased grandfather in 'Artificial'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/19/1205898776/new-yorker-cartoonist-amy-kurzweils-graphic-memoir-artificial-a-love-story</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly stated that Kristen Radtke was a cartoonist for the New Yorker. She's a graphic memoirist and the creative director of The Verge.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears memoir reaches bestseller status a week before it hits shelves</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/18/1206783968/britney-spears-book-the-woman-in-me-hits-bestseller-status</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story reference Spears' growing up in Mississippi. She was born there but grew up in Louisiana. The reference has been removed.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike riding in middle school may boost mental health, study finds</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/10/18/1206583788/bike-riding-in-middle-school-may-boost-mental-health-study-finds</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story referred to Dr. Allan Reiss as a neuropsychologist. He is in fact a neuropsychiatrist.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds killed in explosion at a crowded Gaza hospital</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/17/1206282283/gaza-aid-israel-hamas-biden-visit</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misstated the name of the hospital as the Ali Ahli Baptist Hospital in Gaza. The correct name is the Al Ahli Arab Hospital in Gaza.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement benefits are one of the hang-ups in UAW negotiations</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/13/1205855982/retirement-benefits-are-one-of-the-hang-ups-in-uaw-negotiations</link>
      <description>This story incorrectly stated that at one point, GM had 10 retired workers for every active one. In its 2005 annual report, GM reported 3.2 retirees and surviving spouses for every active employee in the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After historic strike, Kaiser Permanente workers win 21% raise over 4 years</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/10/13/1205788228/kaiser-permanente-strike-contract-deal-reached</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the last name of SEIU United Healthcare Workers President Dave Regan as Reagan.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Issues Evacuation Order For Gaza, Scalise Drops Out, Elijah McClain Verdict</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/13/1198908607/up-first-draft-10-13-2023</link>
      <description>An earlier headline misspelled the last name of Elijah McClain as McCain.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gazans flee their homes after an Israeli evacuation order but have few places to go</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/13/1205672587/israel-warns-evacuate-northern-gaza</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story said Israel ordered Gazans to leave their homes within 24 hours. In fact, Israel did not give a specific deadline for Gazans to evacuate. U.N. officials in Gaza say Israel told them to evacuate within 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Irth' hospital review app aims to take the bias out of giving birth</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/10/13/1205333159/irth-hospital-review-app-aims-to-take-the-bias-out-of-giving-birth</link>
      <description>In a previous version of this story, we included an incorrectly transcribed quote from Kimberly Seals Allers stating that Cedars-Sinai hospital in Los Angeles had a high rate of Black maternal mortality. In fact, the quote did not mention Cedar-Sinai's rate; it refers to a single high-profile Black maternal death. A previous version also incorrectly stated that Seals Allers was from Harlem, N.Y. She is from Queens.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalise drops out of race for speaker of the House, leaving Congress in limbo</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/12/1205627746/scalise-drops-out-of-race-for-speaker-of-the-house-leaving-congress-in-limbo</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story mistakenly said Rep. Steve Scalise defeated Rep. Jim Jordan in a 110-99 vote for House Republicans' speaker nominee. In fact, the vote was 113-99.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Total War: Pharaoh' and 'Star Trek: Infinite': boldly going where we've been before</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/12/1204955269/total-war-pharaoh-star-trek-infinite-strategy</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misstated the name of the fictional Star Trek species Cardassian as Cassardian.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sexual assault victims suing Uber notch a legal victory in their long battle</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/11/1205135476/sexual-assault-victims-suing-uber-notch-a-legal-victory-in-long-battle</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly cited Uber's data on sexual assault and rape as "incidents," rather than "reported incidents."</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant mothers arriving in New York find support, hope — and lots of challenges</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/10/1204273159/migrant-mothers-new-york-bellevue-womens-health-pregnancy</link>
      <description>A previous version of the captions in this story referred to a maternity care unit at the Roosevelt Hotel in New York City. The hotel hosts a medical clinic.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writers union votes to ratify contract, ending one of Hollywood's longest strikes</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/10/1204754706/writers-union-votes-to-ratify-contract-ending-one-of-hollywoods-longest-strikes</link>
      <description>Many NPR newsroom staff are members of SAG-AFTRA but are not part of the bargaining unit that is striking.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One sister survived cancer. Five years later, the other one is still processing it</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/10/1204800583/the-struggles-faced-by-the-siblings-of-cancer-survivors-are-often-overlooked</link>
      <description>A previous version of the broadcast story stated that next month Kristin Long at Boston University will host a convention for siblings like Kayla and Ella in Chicago. The convention is focused on how to support siblings like them.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He watched his family get taken by Hamas fighters. Now he wants Israel to fight back</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/10/1204800604/israeli-hostages-seized-by-hamas-include-a-mother-and-her-children</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled Yosi Shnaider as Yosi Shnaidel.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An 'anti-World's Fair' makes its case: give land back to Native Americans</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/09/1200465128/new-red-order-worlds-unfair-native-americans</link>
      <description>Previous versions of this story incorrectly stated the city that gave back an island as Eureka, Ore. It is Eureka, Calif.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, even with superior intelligence abilities, fails to anticipate Hamas attack</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/09/1204612052/israel-even-with-superior-intelligence-abilities-fails-to-anticipate-hamas-attac</link>
      <description>Earlier digital and audio versions characterized the guest as a top adviser to a former Israeli prime minister. Daniel Levy was an adviser in the government of former Prime Minister Ehud Barak.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Villano Antillano: Tiny Desk Concert</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/06/1200583026/villano-antillano-tiny-desk-concert</link>
      <description>This page originally credited Emilio Mendez as the keyboardist in this Tiny Desk performance. It was Barba Blanca.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New technology uses good old-fashioned wind to power giant cargo vessels</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/05/1200788439/wind-power-cargo-ships-carbon-emissions</link>
      <description>Previous audio and digital versions of this story said the IMO's goal was to cut the shipping industry's greenhouse gas emissions at least in half by 2050. In fact, a revised goal put out earlier this year calls for the industry to reach net zero by mid-century.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's dog Commander has left the White House</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203808674/bidens-dog-commander-has-left-the-white-house</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said the most recent biting incident was on Monday evening. In fact, it was the previous Monday, Sept. 25.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poet Safiya Sinclair reflects on her Rastafari roots and how she cut herself free</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203590575/poet-safiya-sinclair-rasta-how-to-say-babylon</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly quoted Sinclair as saying she realized that poetry could "alkalize" the hurt she was feeling. Sinclair said she realized that poetry cold alchemize that hurt.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles is using AI to predict who might become homeless and help before they do</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1202374047/los-angeles-is-using-ai-to-predict-who-might-become-homeless-and-help-before-the</link>
      <description>Previous photo captions in this story misspelled Valarie Zayas' name as Valaria.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any job can be a climate solutions job: Ask this teacher, electrician or beauty CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203426518/climate-jobs-teacher-electrician-entrepreneur</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story referred to the hair line Braidbetter as Bright Better.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers at Kaiser Permanente are poised to go out on strike</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203547984/workers-at-kaiser-permanente-are-poised-to-go-out-on-strike</link>
      <description>A previous version of the headline misspelled Kaiser Permanente as Kaiser Permanent.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Stewart says his time on 'Star Trek' felt like a ministry</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/04/1203298903/patrick-stewart-star-trek-ministry-picard</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to replace a photo of Patrick Stewart in costume as Jean Luc Picard that had been reversed by the agency that provided it.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did we come to live extremely online? Mommy bloggers, says one writer</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/03/1203033527/how-did-we-come-to-live-extremely-online-mommy-bloggers-says-one-writer</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly used "kid" instead of "kids" in a quote from Taylor Lorenz</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 5 big purchases can save energy — and money — at home</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/03/1196977935/save-money-energy-tips</link>
      <description>A version of this story incorrectly labeled an image of an electric glass cooktop as an induction stove. The image has been removed and updated.

A previous version of this story and its headline incorrectly stated there were six recommendations listed in the story.  There are actually five suggestions in the story.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Carterland' puts a positive spin on an oft-disparaged presidency</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202555558/carterland-movie-jimmy-carter</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly said that President Jimmy Carter appointed Ben Bernanke to head the Federal Reserve. In fact, he appointed Paul Volcker.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's business fraud trial wraps up day one in New York</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1202730320/trump-business-fraud-trial-new-york</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly included Ivanka Trump as among those who are accused of fraud. She is not.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland's dangerous eastern border takes center stage in upcoming elections</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/02/1201688645/poland-belarus-migrants-border-wall-polish-election</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled Bialowieza, the name of a forest and town in Poland.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's in the Army now? A pitch switch aims to get more military recruits</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/10/01/1199543004/recruitment-military</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story misspelled the first name of Lt. Col. Khrysten Grace as Kristen.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger grows over Ukraine's largest Orthodox church, aligned with Moscow despite war</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/30/1201065400/ukraine-russian-orthodox-church-tensions</link>
      <description>In a previous version of this story, we misidentified an image of a monastery in Kyiv and also inaccurately described the location of a protest rally in the Ukrainian capital.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The career and legacy of Sen. Dianne Feinstein</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/29/1202753695/the-career-and-legacy-of-senator-dianne-feinstein</link>
      <description>A previous headline misspelled Sen. Dianne Feinstein's first name as Diane.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's N.Y. business empire is 'greatly at risk' from judge's fraud ruling</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/29/1202534656/trump-fraud-ruling-new-york-business-empire-judge</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story misspelled John Coffee's surname as Coffey.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House chief of staff says it's on House Republicans to avert a shutdown</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/28/1202288527/biden-mccarthy-shutdown-zients</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly said that a government shutdown — rather than proposed budget cuts from House Republicans — would hurt seniors who rely on Meals on Wheels and families with kids in Head Start programs.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a government shutdown would mean for the U.S. military — and national security</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/27/1201956915/government-shutdown-us-military-national-security</link>
      <description>This story has been updated to reflect that Coast Guard members did not get paid during the 2018-2019 government shutdown.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood writers return to work, after a nearly five month strike</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/26/1201936449/writers-strike-end-vote-wga-leadership</link>
      <description>In the audio of this story, as in a previous web version, we incorrectly identify David Goodman as the current president of the WGA West. Goodman is a past president of the WGA West and current co-chair of the WGA's negotiating committee.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Mason on his novel, 'North Woods'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/23/1201306844/daniel-masoon-his-novel-north-woods</link>
      <description>An earlier headline misspelled the last name of Daniel Mason as Masoon.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP rebels recall a distant era when dissidents rose up against 'Czar Cannon'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/09/23/1200992004/motion-to-vacate-matt-gaetz-cannon-1910</link>
      <description>A previous photo caption incorrectly said Republican Rep. Joseph Cannon of Illinois was ousted as House speaker after a revolt in 2010. In fact, he lost much of his power after a revolt in 1910 but remained speaker until the following year.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 18:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
