<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NPR Corrector Bot</title>
    <link>https://www.npr.org/corrections/</link>
    <description>Corrections from NPR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:04:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sandra Day O'Connor, first woman on the Supreme Court, dies</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/12/01/203277264/sandra-day-oconnor-dies</link>
      <description>In the audio, as in a previous version of the web story, we incorrectly say Justice O'Connor was born in Arizona. She was born in El Paso, Texas.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New law gives Texas more power to criminalize undocumented migrants in the state</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/12/01/1216340282/new-law-gives-texas-more-power-to-criminalize-undocumented-migrants-in-the-state</link>
      <description>An earlier description of this story referred to an unrelated story. This story is about legislative efforts in Texas to give state and local law enforcement more power to arrest migrants who cross the southern border illegally.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generations of mothers are at the center of 'A Grandmother Begins The Story'</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/29/1214209282/book-review-michelle-porter-a-grandmother-begins-a-story</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this review incorrectly stated the title of the book. It has been corrected here.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Jonathan Majors' trial begins in New York City, after numerous delays</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/29/1199462210/jonathan-majors-trial</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story incorrectly stated that opening arguments would begin on Thursday. The opening arguments are not expected to begin until jury selection is complete.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Court Ruling Poses A New Threat To The Voting Rights Act's Protections</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/27/1197958202/the-npr-politics-podcast-draft-11-27-2023</link>
      <description>A previous version of this podcast episode incorrectly stated that a local election official in Mississippi's Hinds County had admitted to local media that they did not follow state law and preprint enough ballots for Election Day. This reference was dated and did not refer to the 2022 general election.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilian deaths are being dismissed as 'crisis actors' in Gaza and Israel</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/27/1214451419/civilian-deaths-are-being-dismissed-as-crisis-actors-in-gaza-and-israel</link>
      <description>A previous version of this story incorrectly attributed data about mentions of "Pallywood" to Logically. It should have been attributed to Logically Facts, which is an independent subsidiary of Logically.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 18:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are there too many people in Colorado for gray wolves to thrive?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/29/1215765493/are-there-too-many-people-in-colorado-for-gray-wolves-to-thrive</link>
      <description>An earlier audio version of this story indicated that gray wolves once were wiped out by hunting in Colorado. The corrected version reports only that they were wiped out before they were reintroduced in 2020.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 17:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas abortion case heard before state's highest court, as more women join lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/11/28/1215463289/texas-abortion-lawsuit-texas-supreme-court</link>
      <description>This story was updated at 3:46 p.m. to reflect some of what happened in the hearing.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering Latina public radio journalist Maria Martin dies at 72</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/12/02/1216662361/maria-martin-latino-usa-journalist-dies</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story said Maria Martin was 71 years old. She was 72.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 15:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother of Palestinian student shot in Vermont thought he would be safer in U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2023/11/27/1215362007/vermont-palestinian-shooting-mother-west-bank</link>
      <description>An earlier version of this story identified Hisham Awartani's father as Marwan Awartani. His father's name is Ali Awartani. Marwan is Hisham Awartani's uncle.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
